{
  "topics": [
    {
      "title": "Disney",
      "cards": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "What's the favorite dance move of the aliens in Pizza Planet??",
          "options": [
            {
              "id": "a",
              "text": "Space Hokey Pokey"
            },
            {
              "id": "b",
              "text": "The Claw Cha-Cha"
            },
            {
              "id": "c",
              "text": "Galactic Shuffle"
            }
          ],
          "answer": "The Claw Cha-Cha"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "Why did Kanga bring a pouch to the party?",
          "options": [
            {
              "id": "a",
              "text": "To carry snacks"
            },
            {
              "id": "b",
              "text": "To store honey jars"
            },
            {
              "id": "c",
              "text": "She thought it was a potluck"
            }
          ],
          "answer": "She thought it was a potluck"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "question": "What's the Evil Queen's favorite app?",
          "options": [
            {
              "id": "a",
              "text": "Fairest Filter"
            },
            {
              "id": "b",
              "text": "Poison Apple Pay"
            },
            {
              "id": "c",
              "text": "Wicked Weather"
            }
          ],
          "answer": "Fairest Filter"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "question": "What's Elsa's favorite type of salad?",
          "options": [
            {
              "id": "a",
              "text": "Snow pea salad"
            },
            {
              "id": "b",
              "text": "Frozen greens"
            },
            {
              "id": "c",
              "text": "Iceberg lettuce"
            }
          ],
          "answer": "Frozen greens"
        },
        {
          "id": 5,
          "question": "What is the name of the street rat in Disney's 'Aladdin' ?",
          "options": [
            {
              "id": "a",
              "text": "Remy"
            },
            {
              "id": "b",
              "text": "Jafar"
            },
            {
              "id": "c",
              "text": "Aladdin"
            }
          ],
          "answer": "Aladdin"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Star Wars",
      "cards": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "Who is Luke's Father?",
          "options": [
            {
              "id": "a",
              "text": "Obi-Wan Kenobi"
            },
            {
              "id": "b",
              "text": "Darth Vader"
            },
            {
              "id": "c",
              "text": "Han Solo"
            }
          ],
          "answer": "Darth Vader",
          "currentCard": false
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "Who planet is Jar Jar Binks from?",
          "options": [
            {
              "id": "a",
              "text": "Planet Roo"
            },
            {
              "id": "b",
              "text": "Planet Tahoo"
            },
            {
              "id": "c",
              "text": "Planet Naboo"
            }
          ],
          "answer": "Planet Naboo",
          "currentCard": false
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "question": "What does Yoda say when he plays hide and seek?",
          "options": [
            {
              "id": "a",
              "text": "Hide and seek, I must"
            },
            {
              "id": "b",
              "text": "Found, you are!"
            },
            {
              "id": "c",
              "text": "Seek and hide, I might."
            }
          ],
          "answer": "Found, you are!",
          "currentCard": false
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "question": "Who is Luke Skywalker's Jedi Master?",
          "options": [
            {
              "id": "a",
              "text": "Obi-Wan Kenobi"
            },
            {
              "id": "b",
              "text": "Mace Windu"
            },
            {
              "id": "c",
              "text": "Yoda"
            }
          ],
          "answer": "Obi-Wan Kenobi",
          "currentCard": false
        },
        {
          "id": 5,
          "question": "What is the name of Han Solo's ship?",
          "options": [
            {
              "id": "a",
              "text": "Galactic Phoenix"
            },
            {
              "id": "b",
              "text": "Millenium Falcon"
            },
            {
              "id": "c",
              "text": "Starcruiser Omega"
            }
          ],
          "answer": "Millenium Falcon",
          "currentCard": false
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Marvel",
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "How does Doctor Strange order pizza??",
          "options": [
            {
              "id": "a",
              "text": "Time-traveling to the pizza parlor"
            },
            {
              "id": "b",
              "text": "Using the Eye of Agamotto app"
            },
            {
              "id": "c",
              "text": "Sending a mystical pizza summoning spell"
            }
          ],
          "answer": "Using the Eye of Agamotto app"
        },
        {
          "question": "What's Black Widow's secret talent?",
          "options": [
            {
              "id": "a",
              "text": "Juggling spy gadgets"
            },
            {
              "id": "b",
              "text": "Ballet"
            },
            {
              "id": "c",
              "text": "Competitive knitting"
            }
          ],
          "answer": "Competitive knitting"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is Tony Stark's favorite song??",
          "options": [
            {
              "id": "a",
              "text": "Rocket Man by Elton John"
            },
            {
              "id": "b",
              "text": "Iron Man by Black Sabbath"
            },
            {
              "id": "c",
              "text": "Smooth Operator by Sade"
            }
          ],
          "answer": "Iron Man by Black Sabbath"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is Spider Man's favorite social media platform",
          "options": [
            {
              "id": "a",
              "text": "Webstagram"
            },
            {
              "id": "b",
              "text": "Insta-web"
            },
            {
              "id": "c",
              "text": "Snapweb"
            }
          ],
          "answer": "Webstagram"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "DC",
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "What is Superman's favorite day of the week?",
          "options": [
            {
              "id": "a",
              "text": "Monday(to start the week super)"
            },
            {
              "id": "b",
              "text": "Any day with sun ( for solar charging)"
            },
            {
              "id": "c",
              "text": "Friday ( for a super weekend)"
            }
          ],
          "answer": "Any day with sun ( for solar charging)"
        },
        {
          "question": "How does Martian Manhunter take his tea?",
          "options": [
            {
              "id": "a",
              "text": "Telepathically sweetened"
            },
            {
              "id": "b",
              "text": "Green with envy"
            },
            {
              "id": "c",
              "text": "With a side of Mars-mallows"
            }
          ],
          "answer": "With a side of Mars-mallows"
        },
        {
          "question": "What does Aquaman say when he's feeling down?",
          "options": [
            {
              "id": "a",
              "text": "I need some fish therapy"
            },
            {
              "id": "b",
              "text": "I'm in over my head"
            },
            {
              "id": "c",
              "text": "Water you gonna do?"
            }
          ],
          "answer": "I'm in over my head"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}